let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Kate:  Do you have __________(any/some) brothers or sisters?<br>John:  No, I don't, but I have __________(any/some) cousins.",
    answer: "Any , Some",
    options: [
      "Any , Some",
      "Some , Some",
      "Any , Any",
      "Some , Any"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Mary:  Do you have __________(any/some) idea of how to do this exercise?<br> Peter: No, I have no idea, but my mum gave __________(any/some) books to study, maybe the answer is there!",
    answer: "Any , Some",
    options: [
      "Some , Some",
      "Any , Any",
      "Any , Some",
      "Some , Any"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Julia ate ________(a little/a few) rice, she wasn't very hungry.",
    answer: "A little",
    options: [
      "A few",
      "A little",
      "All of above",
      "None of above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "She found ________(a little/a few) cookies under her bed.",
    answer: "A few",
    options: [
      "A few",
      "A little",
      "All of above",
      "None of above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "I want to save ________(a little/a few) money to buy a present for my mother.",
    answer: "A little",
    options: [
      "A few",
      "Little",
      "Few",
      "A little"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Robert gave me ________(a little/a few) coins to buy a sweater,<br> it is not enough!",
    answer: "A few",
    options: [
      "A little",
      "Few",
      "A few",
      "None of above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Claire has ________(many/much) brothers but only one sister.",
    answer: "Many",
    options: [
      "Much",
      "Many",
      "All of above",
      "None of above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "I don't have ________(many/much) time,<br> I can't wait for you",
    answer: "Much",
    options: [
      "Much",
      "Many",
      "All of above",
      "None of above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Tom works ________(many/much/little/few) hours every day,<br> that is why he is always tired.",
    answer: "Many",
    options: [
      "Few",
      "Little",
      "Much",
      "Many"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Lisa doesn't drink ________(many/much/Few) water when she eats.",
    answer: "Much",
    options: [
      "Few",
      "Many",
      "Much",
      "None of above"
    ]
  },
];